# **Ederson Arrieta**

Jr.Software Developer

### **Contact information**

#### Cell:

(+506) 8435 5028

#### Email:

earrietam1997@gmail.com

#### Adress:

Ulloa, Heredia Costa Rica.

#### Online CV:

https://eder126.github.io/Curriculum/

# **Summary**

Worked in Amazon for nearly 3 years in multiple fields, maintaining consistent metrics during my time, succeeding and learning as an integral part of my professional growth.

Once I decided to move forward from this opportunity, I focused on continuing my studies in the field of programming at Cenfotec, as I look forward to developing my own ideas in video games, as a personal goal.

Never have I rejected the opportunity to perform a task and complete the same. I have always believed that attitude and manners make the man, and based on my experience, every task can be successfully completed if the right mentality is set.

# **Experience**

# **MBO Specialist**

#### **Amazon**

Dec. 2016 to May 2018

- The field of Marketplace Business
   Operation Specialist provided the
   opportunity to work with people from
   both Bangladesh, India and Seattle, US
   in improving internal procedures in
   regards to user experience using the
   Vendor Central platform.
- Worked with sensitive high brand information to improve the customers experience when shopping in the Amazon website.
- Functioned as a Point of Contact in regards to the SOP's of a process in charge of reviewing legitimacy of brands and their products for the Amazon website.

#### **Vendor Central Associate**

#### Amazon

Jun. 2016 to Dec. 2016

- Provided assistance in phone and email contacts from Amazon
   Vendors from the Vendors program.
- Maintained consistent metrics in regards to customer satisfaction.
- Assisted temporarily as a POC to peers in regards to our policies and procedures.
- Assisted temporarily as a Supervisor to take control of escalations and find solutions to said situations.

# **Advantage Associate**

#### Amazon

Jan. 2016 to Jun. 2016

- Formed part of a new team in charge of establishing the standard procedure and metrics to pursue when dealing with Vendors of the Amazon Advantage program.
- Handled alongside the team the first ever phone contacts for Amazon Advantage Vendors in the world.
- Helped restructure broken/imperfect procedures up to a point where they could be considered reliable and standard.

## **Education**

#### **Cenfotec University**

#### Tecnical degree in Software Engineering

- Design Pattern Programming
   Project: Board game inspired by Snakes and Ladders with turn
   based combat against PC opponent. Developed with: Java, JavaFx.
- Data Structures
  - Project: School registration system, using mainly pointers to gather detailed reports. Developed with: C++.
- Proyecto 2
  - Project: Food delivery service/web application trying to compete against Rappi, Uber Eats and Glovo. Developed with: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C#, SQL. APIs: Twilio, SendGrid, IronPDF, GMaps.
- Proyecto 1
  - Project: Online library trying to compete against Amazon. Focused on Online shopping, either physical or digital, and online Lecture Clubs. Developed with: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, MongoDB.

# **Technologies**

- .NET.
- Java, JavaFx.
- HTML/CSS, Node, Express, MongoDB.
- Twilio, SendGrid, IronPDF, GMaps.
- PostMan, Git, AzureDevOps, Visual Paradigm, Visual Studio.

### **Skills**

- · Spanish native.
- English 90%.
- · Positive attitude.
- · Problem solver.
- Fast learner and adaptable to new circumstances.
- Willing to step in unknown territory in order to
  learn